April yes would you like to remove the
next number
what do we have
space time would you also like to remove
the 4A and B
what do we have there a little
space-time graph
all right
now let us explain we have talked about
this briefly before
oh you may say thank you very much
the idea
is
you already know
from what you call
your science of relativity
or some of you may not know this
that there is an effect in your reality
called time dilation
that when you move let's say in a
spaceship
faster and faster and faster and faster
and approach what you call the speed of
light
which is simply in a sense the border of
your particular reality
doesn't mean you can't actually travel
faster it's just the border of your
particular reality just the threshold
but in your physical reality while you
travel in your physical reality up to
the speed of light
the phenomenon called time dilation is
noticed to occur what this simply means
is the faster you move in Space the
slower you move in time
slows down
this is what creates the twin paradox as
many of your scientists have expressed
it so that if you imagine there are two
twins that are the same age and one
steps into a spacecraft and goes out
into the stars and travels very close to
the speed of light time for them on the
ship will slow down to the point that
when they come back they may actually be
many many many years younger than the
twin who stayed on Earth who will have
aged in the meantime
the idea that understanding this is to
understanding space time as a 100 idea
there can only be 100 space time so if
you are traveling
at 50 percent
of the speed of light
then the idea is is that you are using
up that much space
there's only 50 percent of time left
so you can only experience half the time
the closer you travel to the speed of
light you're using up more and more of
the space of space-time and there is
less and less of the time left
so you only experience a little bit of
it so if you're traveling at 99 you're
only experiencing one percent of time
and 99 of space conversely when you're
standing perfectly still as most of you
are right now you're experiencing almost
all of time and very little of space at
all you're not moving around
so it's always a shared idea
whatever you use of time you can only
have that much space left whatever you
use of space you only have that much
time to use
the graph shows you this in this way the
line is all of time at one end all of
space at the other end and when you
start moving and expanding your use of
space from zero into a cone that widens
then you have very little time left but
when you go the other way and use all of
the idea the other way then the cone
moves in the other direction it's just
an expansion cone I'm using very little
here I'm using a lot here using very
little of this when I'm using a lot of
this but when I'm using a little of this
I'm using a lot of that
so it's just a double cone going in this
way to show you when you are using a
little bit of this or a lot of that
you follow me so far
all right now
this is also the key to building a
space-time antenna
a device that actually uses space-time
energy that you can then learn to
translate into different forms of energy
if you wish such as electricity or light
or heat or whatever you wish to do with
it the space-time antenna
actually takes the form of this graph of
the two intersecting cones
so if you imagine in your mind right now
let's say
made out of a spiral copper wire or a
spiral tube imagine starting on the
ground and imagine
bringing the tube around in a circle and
then spiraling it upward getting smaller
and smaller in circumference you're
describing a cone you're spiraling up to
the tip of the cone however High you
want the cone to be doesn't matter
however why you want to start doesn't
matter right now for the purpose of this
illustration it will matter later in
terms of fine-tuning the geometry to get
the right effect but right now just for
the purpose of this illustration just
imagine starting on the ground start
spiraling your tube around and around
and around smaller smaller until you
have a cone made up out of a spiral tube
at the top at the very tip of the cone
then take that tube and move it out to
the same diameter as the base of the
cone and start spiraling your way down
through the other cone so when you
spiral it up leave some gaps in between
the tube so that when you spiral down
you can go through those gaps and
actually have the two cones
interpenetrating until you get all the
way down now you're inside the base of
the first cone creating a downward
facing cone and you get down to the tip
at the bottom and then bring that out
and connect it to the base of the other
cone
now you have two interpenetrating cones
one facing up one pointing down
in a sense it's almost like the idea of
the Solomon Seal or what you now call
the Jewish star the six-pointed star if
you look at it simply flat on it will
sort of appear a little bit like this
idea although not quite exactly but it's
the idea of two interpenetrating
triangles
when you create this kind of a resonant
device and you do it
where the cones are actually angled at
their apices at 33 degrees you will be
able to actually have a space time
antenna
depending upon the quality of your
material the number of windings the size
of the cone and what have you and other
conditions
you can actually cause this cone with a
little bit of an electrical charge to
start resonating at a certain frequency
that will amplify that energy by drawing
down from space-time energy and thus
then giving out more energy than you're
putting in
so this diagram the space-time diagram
shows you literally graphically how to
create a space-time antenna for those of
you who might be interested in playing
with this idea
as a fun home experiment
well this is where our children start
so have some fun explore with it if you
wish it's up to you or use this idea by
imagining it simply in your imagination
and play with what that shape does when
you get it in your mind's eye in terms
of opening you up to other levels of
communication as well because you can
use it that way too you don't have to
physicalize it to get an effect within
your own Consciousness but you can
physicalize it to get an effect in
physical reality so play with it however
you wish
if you also do it in your mind and you
see that shape in your mind if you can
also learn to view it
three-dimensionally and start turning it
rotating it in your mind and see it in
different angles that will absolutely
heighten and increase your ability
that's happened to other dimensional
frequencies as well
so play with this however you wish and
have fun have fun have fun